interactiveone.com 2017-01-26

# Privacy - Interactive One

**_Last revised April 20, 2015_**  
Interactive One, LLC (“IONE,” also referred to as “we,” “our,” or “us”), offers access to its services (“Services”) through a network of related digital content and social networking websites and platforms (accessed, and/or used, via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise), that are owned and operated by IONE (each, a “Site” and collectively, the “Sites”). This Privacy Policy describes the type of information we or third parties may collect from you while you visit or otherwise interact with the Sites and how we may use and share that information. This Privacy Policy also explains the choices you can make about the ways this information is used by us. The term Sites when used herein refers to those IONE sites, Services, interactive features, and applications that post or link to this Privacy Policy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review the Terms of Service provided at each Site, which governs your use of the Sites. Since IONE offers many different Services, additional terms or requirements may apply to certain service offerings and these additional terms will accompany such offering. By accessing and using any of the Sites (including, without limitation, any social networking features, applications, communities or other interactive content offered on the Sites) and Services, you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service provided on the Site. Some Services are provided on mobile and wireless devices and this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply, unless otherwise indicated. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service, please do not use the Site or the Services. Please note that certain features or Services discussed in this Privacy Policy may not be offered on the Sites at any particular time.

## APPLICABILITY AND USER RESTRICTIONS

Unless specifically stated otherwise, this Privacy Policy applies to information collected on the Sites and Services, which also may be governed by separate or additional policies and may not apply to information about you collected by our affiliated providers, third party web sites (e.g., ad serving and tracking services), third party owned applications or offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from the Sites. The information collected or received by such affiliated providers, third parties and third party owned applications are subject to their own respective privacy policies, which we encourage you to review. We are not responsible for compliance with other websites’ privacy policies or practices.

The Sites are not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13). In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), we use reasonable commercial efforts to adhere to the prohibition on the collection of personal information online from children under the age of thirteen (13) without first obtaining verifiable parental consent. At a minimum, the Sites prohibit registration by, and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, anyone under the age of thirteen (13). Site use and membership is void where prohibited by law.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

Whether you are a Site visitor, user of a particular Service, or a registered member, we take certain steps to protect your information. Collection of information is usually grouped into three categories: Personal Information, which is information that is personally identifiable to a specific visitor (further defined below), non personally identifiable information, which is information that is passively collected and information you may providethat is traceable to a computer or device but does not include Personal Information and is therefore not traceable back to you and cannot be used to identify a specific individual (further defined below) and aggregate information, which is general demographic information collected from large numbers of Site visitors that does not identify any individual member and is aggregated into statistical data and information. We may use or disclose non personal and aggregate information about you with third parties for any purpose. Depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge third parties for this information, or limit the third parties’ use of such information.

Some of the ads you receive on Site pages are customized based on predictions about your interests generated from your visits to the Sites (“Behavioral Advertising”). IONE adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising (the “Principles”), developed by leading industry associations to apply consumer-friendly standards to online behavioral advertising across the Internet and mobile devices. To learn more about the Principles, and how to opt-out of Behavioral Advertising please go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

### User Content

Please note that whenever you publicly disclose information about yourself online (e.g., through email, social networking platforms, forums, message boards, chat areas, or similar web pages), such information may be collected, exported and used by people that you do not know. Posting personal information in public places may result in unsolicited communications, including unwanted email messages or other forms of contact. Always be smart about the information you provide online. We bear no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information you may disclose on the Sites.

### Personal Information

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means information collected online about an individual that can be used to distinguish or trace an individual’s identity either alone, or in combination with other personal or identifying information that is linked or linkable to a specific individual, such as a first and last name, a physical street address, an e-mail address, a telephone number, a social security number, or any other information that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual. You can browse the Sites without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. However, there are certain features and services (including social networking) that may not be available for your use without providing Personal Information. If you choose to provide us with Personal Information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers. Further, you consent to e-mail or other marketing communications sent by us, unless you unsubscribe from such messages or opt-out, as described below.

#### Non-Personal Information

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Non Personal Information” means and may include, but is not limited to, information collected passively through the use of technology such as cookies, beacons, algorithms as well as information you provide that is not traceable back to you and cannot be used to identify a specific individual, including: gender, age, marital status, household income, city and state, listening and streaming metrics, when such user provided information is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. IONE may also use server logs and capture certain Non Personal Information such as the operating system being used, or the IP address or other unique identifiers, such as Device Identifiers (defined below). This Non Personal Information is generally used to help IONE plan system enhancements and understand which content and Services are compatible with users’ web browsing systems. It is also used to create anonymous reporting of Non Personal Information for internal and external clients; create aggregated portraits of the users of the Services that represent anonymous demographic information but not Personally Identifiable Information. This Aggregated Information is used among other things, to determine trends and needs and also to supply market research to potential partners to help them understand who the visitors of the Sites and Services are and to Your IP address is a number that is assigned by your Internet service provider to your computer to identify your location. .A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your device used to access the Site or Services and our computers identify your device by its Device Identifiers. When IONE associates Non Personal Information or a Device Identifier with Personal Information, IONE will treat it as Personal Information in accordance with this policy for so long as the information is combined.

#### Mobile Apps

Certain of IONE’s online Services can be accessed from mobile devices (“Mobile Apps”). If you use an IONE Mobile App, the information you submit through the Mobile App and the information we may collect through the use of cookies and other tracking devices and otherwise (as detailed elsewhere throughout this Privacy Policy) is be governed by this Privacy Policy. Certain Mobile Apps and other online Services require your location information for the feature to work. Please select the Mobile App from within your device’s Settings tab for information about how to opt out of providing location information. When you use a Mobile App or view content on the Sites we may automatically collect and store the same types of information collected via the Sites. A Mobile App may contain a unique Mobile App number, which we may use to access the performance of our Mobile App or other online Services, provide tech support, conduct research, generate analytics, to address internal online service operations and respond to your needs. This information may also be used by us to personalize the service offerings and advertising you receive through our Mobile App. In particular, IONE’s streaming Mobile Apps may feature third party proprietary software which can track your streaming and/or listening preferences to contribute to market research. To learn how to opt out, please see information available in the Settings tab. IONE may share your usage and personal information with operating systems, carriers and platform providers and /or other mobile apps either operated by us or third parties, as well as any other entities described in any particular Mobile App. Some Mobile Apps may be supported via advertising and collect data to help the online service serve ads. IONE may work with third party analytic companies to understand how and how often the service is being used. We may also work with advertisers and third party advertising networks.

#### Registration

Certain features and Services of the Sites may require you to first complete a registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to provide certain Personal Information. We may use this information to contact you about the services on our Site in which you have expressed interest. In addition to Personal Information collected for registration purposes, we may collect and store the following:

(a) your responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on the Sites;

(b) information about the Sites’ Services or features that you use, and how frequently you use them;

(c) commercial transaction-related information (such as credit card or other preferred means of payment, billing or shipping information, or a history of products purchased through the Sites);

(d) your responses to or entries for surveys, sweepstakes, and contests and requests for services, products, newsletters or information;

(e) customer service information about you as a user of a Site, including any suggestions you submit to us for review;

(f) community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our Sites, and correspondence sent to us;

(g) your activity on the Sites, including adding a friend, sharing a photo or video, or accessing an application)

### Profile and Preference Information

So that you can make the most of our social networking features, your member name, profile photo and certain other profile information associated with your account with a Site or with any third party sites shared by you through a Site will not be private. Depending on your privacy settings, you can control other information shared on your member page. If you do not wish to share photos of yourself with other members, then delete them or do not post them.

### Cookies

To enhance your experience with the Sites, we may use “cookies.” Cookies are small data files that we place in your computer’s browser when you visit the Sites. We may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as tracking usage patterns, measuring the effectiveness of advertising, to help serve advertisements, limiting multiple responses and registrations, facilitating your ability to navigate the Sites, and as part of a verification or screening process. Cookies automatically identify your web browser whenever you visit the Sites, help us determine which areas are popular and further personalize your experience on the Sites. If you do not wish to allow for use of cookies, you can generally opt-out of providing this information by setting your browser to reject cookies. However, please be aware that some areas of the Sites may not provide you with an acceptable user experience if you have disabled the use of cookies. Please refer to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) for more information.

### Web Beacons and Similar Technologies

The Sites and our e-mail messages may contain a small graphic image called a web beacon that monitors and collects certain limited information about the viewer of the web page or e-mail message. Web beacons typically are very small (generally 1-by-1 pixel) and invisible to the user, but, in general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page or e-mail message, including an advertisement or HTML content, can act as a web beacon. We may use web beacons or similar technologies for a number of purposes, including without limitation, to count visitors to our web pages or to monitor how our users navigate the Sites, and we may include web beacons or similar technologies in e-mails in order to count how many e-mails (or particular articles, links, etc.) that we send are actually opened. Additionally, our advertising providers may use web beacons or similar technologies to personalize and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements using data gathered over time from users of the Sites. If you would like more information about the information collection practices of some of these third party advertising companies and to learn which of these companies allow you to opt out of this type of information collection, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### IP Address and Log Files

Upon visiting the Sites, we may collect and store your browser type and IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Sites, to help identify and analyze user trends, to customize content and advertisements offered to you, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

## INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM THIRD PARTIES

In addition to information that you provide or we collect through the Sites and Services, we may verify or collect certain information about you from third parties. We may combine this third party information with information we have already collected from you via the Site and Services and use this information for a variety of reasons including customizing content made available to you, provide promotions and marketing offers tailored to your preferences and to improve the content of the Sites and to help identify and analyze user trends, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Information received from third parties may include the following:

(a) your activity on certain third party sites or services for which you have consented to connect or share through your account on a Site;

(b) information from other companies, such as demographic and traffic data; and

(c) other information from your interaction with our Sites, services, content and advertising, collected by third party advertisers or providers including computer and/or mobile device connection and location information, browser type, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information.

## SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

### Third Party Content

When you are visiting the Sites, certain content may be served directly by third parties. This third party content may use cookies, web beacons, Javascript or other technologies. We do not have access to or control the use of such technology by third parties, including the information they collect or how they use such information.

### Third Party Applications and Websites

IONE may not own or operate all applications, Services or websites (e.g., games or tools) accessible through the Sites, or otherwise made available to you by IONE. Similarly, data may be collected through applications owned or operated by different parties on a particular device or through a particular application for the purpose of delivering ads or providing advertising related services or statistical reporting. As a result, when you use these third party applications or websites, we may share your information along with the location of your computer or mobile device to enable your use of such services and for age verification and security purposes, and to allow visitors to contribute to marketing research via third party measurement software included within the application among other purposes. IONE may offer you the option to connect your member profile and activity on the Sites with certain third party services such as Facebook, or Twitter (“Third Party Services”). When you consent to publish your information or activity on the Sites to any Third Party Services, such information will be viewable by the communities on such Third Party Services and may be used by such Third Party Services in accordance with their posted privacy practices, or if another member in your friend list uses a third party application or website, it may receive your non-private member information so that you may be separately linked with your friend. If third party applications or websites seeks any further information, your consent should be requested. We cannot guarantee that such applications or websites will follow our privacy practices, so we encourage you to always review their information sharing policies and to report any application or website that may be in violation of our privacy practices.

### Online Shopping Services

The Sites may offer shopping services either directly or through a partner that operates a service under contract with us. If a Site offers shopping or other commercial services, the customer order form will ask you to provide certain Personal Information, including credit card or other payment data. The financial information that you provide will be used by IONE or its partners to bill you for products and services that you request and for any other uses to which you have consented. By giving the Site your payment data and related Personal Information, you are authorizing us to give that information to the merchant and credit card company and/or you are authorizing IONE’s partner directly to confirm and fulfill your order. In addition, IONE and/or our partners will use contact information from the order form to fulfill your orders and for customer service purposes. IONE will not otherwise use or distribute your financial information without your prior approval.

### Other Third Parties

IONE may share or transfer the information it collects with third parties including vendors, service providers, advertisers, contractors and IONE agents acting on behalf of IONE and who help to operate the Sites. Examples of such service providers include third parties that provide processing, storage, technical or fulfilment services, data analysis, customer service and emails, audio and video streaming, IONE my provide these companies with access to user information, including Personal Information, to carry out the services they are performing for you and IONE. While IONE may use third party analytics providers to evaluate and provide IONE with information about the Sites and Services, the Sites audience and Sites content, IONE does not share Personal Information with these analytics service providers, but the providers may set and access their own cookies, web beacons and embedded scripts on your device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, including Non Personal Information.

Our employees, agents and contractors must have a “need-to-know” business reason to obtain access to your Personal Information. We may share your Personal Information with those who help us manage or provide content or other services for the Sites (e.g., forum administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses, data processing), or with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes. Such outside contractors, agents or sponsors may temporarily store some information on their servers, but they may only use your Personal Information to provide the Sites with a specific service and not for any other purpose without your consent. We may also provide your Personal Information to a third party where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires sharing your Personal Information. We also may share your Personal Information with any affiliated companies and partners if we have a business reason to do so.

### Legal Compliance

We may access or disclose your Personal Information without your consent in order to: (i) protect or defend our legal rights or property, including those of our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of other users of the Sites or members of the public, including responding to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if any Site is sold to or merges with another company not owned by or affiliated with IONE, we may transfer your Personal Information to any acquiring or merging party as part of that transaction.

## YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES

The following sub-headings apply only to those Sites for which user registration is available.

### Access to Personal Information

You have the opportunity to correct, update or remove Personal Information you have provided to us at any time. Upon entering any Site, you may sign in using your previously issued login name and password. After signing in, click on “My Page” and you will have the option of either modifying or deleting your member profile settings through the “Edit Profile” or “My Account” links. If you have forgotten your login name or password, click the “Forgot your password?” link, and following verification, your login name and/or password will be sent to your email address.

#### Activity Associated with Your Member Name

Your member name is displayed to other members throughout the Sites and depending on your activity (e.g., blogging) on any Sites, may also be available to the public. All of your activity on our Sites is traceable to your member name. Therefore, if you associate your name with your member name, the people to whom you have revealed your name will be able to personally identify your Site activities.

### Opt-Out

You may opt-out of receiving e-mail communications from us at any time by either following the instructions to unsubscribe within an email you receive from this Site or by logging in to your account and selecting “Email Alerts” under the “My Account” link. As explained above, if you choose not to provide us with information sought on registration or sign up forms, it is possible that you will not be able to access or use certain features of certain Sites.

### Your Member Profile

When you register with certain Sites, you may set up your member profile, upload photos, provide additional information, search, add friends, send messages, perform searches and engage in other activities. Information transmitted during such activities is collected so that the IONE may provide you with services and personalize certain features. Any content you post on the Sites is at your own risk. Certain privacy options exist on the Sites that allow you to limit access to your profile. However, such privacy options are not always available or perfect. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. Furthermore, the IONE cannot control the actions of third parties with whom you choose to share your profile or Personal Information. Because of the foregoing, the IONE does not guarantee that any content or personal information you post on a Site will not be accessible by unauthorized persons. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your user content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your user content. Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on any Site is a violation of the Site’s Terms of Use and should be reported to memberadvocate@interactiveone.com.

### Friend Referrals

The Sites may allow you invite a friend to view or use certain features or services Sites, including online shopping services. To refer a friend, information including your friend’s email address is required. Such information is collected and stored to send this one-time invitation, to allow for your friend’s registration and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [memberadvocate@interactiveone.com](mailto:memberadvocate@interactiveone.com) to request that we remove this information from our records.

## SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

IONE employs reasonable security measures consistent with standard industry practice to secure information collected through IONE Sites. We also use internal protections to limit access to your Personal Information to only those people who need the information to perform a specific request. However, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (e.g., as a result of unauthorized or otherwise unlawful third party access), and you transmit such information to us at your own risk.

#### Account Protection

Your member profile is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this information. Please use a unique combination of numbers, letters and special characters and do not disclose your Site password to anyone for greater protection. If you share your computer with other people, or use a publicly accessible computer, sign out of your account and close your browser window when you are done. If you do share your password or your Personal Information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken under your member profile. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your Personal Information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. If your password has been compromised for any reason, we encourage you to change it immediately or notify us to change your password on your behalf.

#### **If Abuse Occurs**

Although we make every effort to ensure that our e-mail list is safe, the Internet is such that we cannot guarantee that our list is invulnerable to attacks. If you believe there has been a breach of our security, please contact us at once at memberadvocate@interactiveone.com.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy’s new effective date. We encourage you to refer to visit this Privacy Policy frequently to stay informed regarding our current privacy practices. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your activity on our Company Sites.

As the owner of this Site, the Company retains all ownership rights to the information collected at this Site. In the event the Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred.

## CONTACTING US

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time by email at memberadvocate@interactiveone.com or at Privacy Request, c/o Interactive One LLC, 850 Third Avenue, Third Floor, New York, NY 10022, USA.

  1. 8, 4/20/2015
